很久以前  有一個女孩叫泰莎
Once upon a time, there was a girl named Tessa
她有一個夢想
who had a dream.
整日忙碌  卻一無所獲
Workin' all day, don't do a thing
其實你坐在駕駛座  可以掌控自己的生活
Life's what you make it, you're in the driver's seat
加大油門  擰動點火
Rev your engine, crank the ignition
給我鑰匙  你怎樣都無法阻止我
Give me the key, don't need your permission
媽媽總是說
Momma always told me
生活中沒什麼好怕的
There's nothin' in this life to fear
從懵懵懂懂到無所不能  你將會想念現在的我
You're gonna miss me zero to sixty
把生活拉回正軌
Kickin' it into gear
是我坐在駕駛座  掌控著生活
I'm in control and behind the wheel
想去哪裏  就將一往無前
And I'm gonna steer where I want to steer
是我坐在駕駛座  掌控著生活
I'm in control and behind the wheel
想去哪裏  就將一往無前
And I'm gonna steer where I'm gonna steer
加足馬力
Go full throttle
全速前進
Pedal to the metal
沒什麼好怕的
Nothin' to fear
讓自己進入正軌
Get yourself in gear
加足馬力
And go full throttle
Go full throttle
鬆開離合  飛速前進
Pop out the clutch get this thing in drive
如果你不想成為匆匆過客
Don't want to be a passenger who's just cruisin' by
刮到保險杠  也沒關係
Scratch the bumper it doesn't matter
但是這個故事  是關於她的現實生活
But this is a story about her reality.
泰莎  你最好快點  那個老巫婆剛到了
Better hurry, Tessa, the wicked witch just arrived.
泰莎
Tessa!
-泰莎  泰莎  泰莎  -沒關係  這兒有我呢
- Tessa! Tessa! Tessa! - It's alright, I got this.
謝謝你  喬
Thanks, Joe.
她正度假  可能脾氣會好點
Hey, maybe she gets nicer on vacation.
我的天哪  泰莎
Holy crapola, Tessa!
你把我最喜歡的包磨壞了
You scuffed my favorite bag.
對不起  迪萬  要拿的東西太多了
I-I'm sorry, Divine,this is a lot to carry.
泰莎  我們可是一起拿呢
Well, we're all pitching in, Tessa.
我叫輛行李車
I'll ring the cart...
不要
No.
我才不會給這些貪婪的人小費呢
No way am I tipping those vultures.
不要  就不
No! No!
小心看著點閃閃
Be extra careful with Sparkles.
誰是好狗狗呀
Who's a good dog?
-誰是好狗狗  -迪萬
- Who's a good dog? - Divine?
怎麼了
What? Yes?
他已經死了
He's dead.
他還活在我心裏呢  泰莎
Not in my heart, Tessa.
媽
Mom!
貴賓公主套餐還包括個化妝舞會
The VIP Princess package includes a costume party,
裏德·韋斯特也會出席
and Reed West is performing!
讓我看看
Let me see!
讓一讓
Over here. Must you...
更好的是  我們還有
Even better, we get our own private
七分鐘和裏德·韋斯特單獨見面
7-minute Reed West encounter!
我們在裏面可不能只待七分鐘  雅典娜
We're in it for a lot more than seven minutes, Athena!
我們是衝著贏來的
We're here to win.
好  我馬上就到
Okay, I'll-- I'll be there in a minute.
你會是 下一個
{\fr5\shad4\c&HBD870E&\3c&HD0B694&\4c&H4B474A&\fn方正行楷简体\b1\i1\pos(212.887,172.859)}灰姑娘嗎
週五試鏡
有個游泳池  雅典娜  你要穿上比基尼
Oh, a pool. Athena, you need to put on your bikini
-坐在泳池邊  -好的
- and sit by that pool. - Okay.
沒說你  奧林匹亞
Uh, not you, Olympia.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
這些女孩看著很專業啊
These girls look like pros.
她們身上可沒流淌著
They don't have superstar's blood
巨星的血液
coursing through their veins.
記住  姑娘們  你們是麥當娜的第三代表親
Remember, girls, you're Madonna's third cousins
隔了兩輩
twice removed.
也沒多少血緣關係
Not a lot of blood.
血緣就是血緣
Blood is blood.
如果我年輕10歲
If I were 10 years younger,
我就自己上了
I'd snag that role myself.
不好  珍妮特來了
Uh-oh, Janet's here.
她父母還讓她去了紐約的音樂訓練營
Her parents send her to music camp in New York.
姑娘們  貴賓午宴上見
See you ladies at the VIP lunch.
我都等不及了
Ah, can't wait!
碧安卡也在這兒
Bianca's here too!
勞倫
Lauren!
迪萬
Divine!
你換了個臉
I almost didn't recognize you
我都差點沒認出來你
with your new face.
你想要那兒的電話嗎
Would you like the number?
他們也做抽脂
They do lipo as well.
我都忘了你有多詼諧了
I'd forgotten how dreadfully witty you are.
我們都很期待這個星期的活動
So we're really excited about this week.
對不對  碧安卡
Right, Bianca?
親愛的  寶貝
Sweetheart? Darling?
碧安卡  親愛的
Bianca, sweetheart.
是啊  太興奮了
Yeah. So excited.
她是不是有點懶散啊
She's a bit of a slug, isn't she?
她一直在排練
She's been rehearsing.
你就帶了一個助手
You've only brought one assistant.
真是勇敢
So brave.
我不是她助手
Oh, uh, I'm not her assistant,
我是她的繼女
I'm her stepdaughter.
-泰莎  -什麼
- Uhh, Tessa? - Yeah?
你能去把閃閃帶過來嗎
Could you please go get Sparkles?
-帶閃閃來  -好  迪萬  我馬上去
- Get Sparkles! - Yes, right away, Divine.
謝謝你
Thank you.
她對於自己
She's a bit sensitive
在生活中的位置有點敏感
about her position in life.
跟你聊天很有意思
Well, it's been fascinating,
但是  現在我感覺無聊了
but, mm, now I'm bored.
泰莎  我們走
Tessa, we're on the move!
馬上來
Right away!
裏德
Oh, Reed,
為了你  我賣器官都行
I would sell body parts for you.
值錢的那些
Good ones.
真噁心  別流口水了  奧林匹亞
Ugh, gross. Stop drooling, Olympia.
為了他  賣個腎絕對值了
He's definitely worth a kidney.
他看起來有女朋友了  那個女孩是誰
He looks taken. Who's the girl?
哈珀·哈爾斯頓
Ugh. Harper Halston.
-是那個女繼承人  -她可真漂亮
- The heiress. - She's so pretty.
皇家湖度假村是她家的
Her family owns Royal Lagoon Resorts.
這場海選由他們主辦
They're holding the audition contest.
你要不是忙著給化油器抹油什麼的
You'd know all this if you weren't so busy
你就知道了
greasing up carburetors or whatever.
你指我的工作
You mean my job.
泰莎  這個星期可不一樣
Not this week, Tessa.
你來這裏是要幫雅典娜和奧林匹亞
You're here to help Athena and Olympia
達成一個目標
focus on one thing,
那就是迷倒裏德  當上主角
dazzling Reed and winning the lead role.
你們其中一個將在音樂劇中擔任主演
One of you girls is going to star in the musical,
拿下唱片合約
win that recording contract,
讓我驕傲
and do me proud.
我給你們起女神的名字是有原因的
I named you after goddesses for a reason.
什麼音樂劇
What's the musical?
-《灰姑娘》  -《灰姑娘》
- Cinderella. - Cinderella.
好吧  還真有點諷刺
Okay, that's kind of ironic.
你  跟我來
You follow me.
是的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
你會愛上你的小房間
You are going to love your little room.
就在這邊
Okay, so it's right this way.
好的
Okay, all right.
就跟有你自己的私人溫泉似的
It's just like having your own spa.
就在這後面
Right through here.
就是這兒
Here we go.
就在樓梯下  又漂亮又舒適
Nice and cozy, under the stairs.
所以說我是哈利·波特
So I'm Harry Potter.
沒錯
Exactly.
小心看著大門
Now, um, be careful of the gate,
門是從外面鎖的
because it locks from the outside.
別告訴任何人你在這裏  好嗎
A-And don't tell anyone you're here, okay?
讓你住這兒  我可要惹大麻煩了
Oh, I'm going to get into so much trouble for this.
別擔心  這種事兒我也不會發動態的
Don't worry, it's not exactly something I'll Instagram.
也是
Yeah.
謝謝
Thanks.
奧林匹亞  別弄了
Olympia, stop that!
太噁心了  停下
That's disgusting! Stop it!
天哪  你幹什麼呢
Oh, my God, what are you doing?
住手  別吃那個
Stop it! Don't eat that!
我真想不到你這麼讓我丟臉
I cannot believe you're humiliating me this way!
天哪
Oh, dear.
-真的準備好了  -我覺得你勝券在握
-Like really ready. -I think you have this in the bag.
我從來沒見過這麼多呆滯的女孩
I've never seen such a dull group of girls.
-你還記得珍妮特嗎  -記得 珍  你好
- You remember Janet? - Oh, yes, oh, Jane, hello.
-是珍妮特  -你掉了
- It's Janet. - Oh, you dropped some--
泰莎  泰莎
Tess-- Tess-- Ah!
泰莎
Ow. Tessa.
女士們
Ladies...
非常感謝
Thank you so much.
她有點遲鈍
She's-- She's a little slow,
但你知道  她聞起來很香
but you know, she smells good,
所以我們把她留在身邊
so we keep her around.
你太壞了
You're so bad!
歡迎光臨  貴賓們
Welcome, VIPs.
就這麼一眼看過去
You know, by the looks of this crowd,
我還以為VIP的意思是  非常漂亮的人
you'd think VIP stands for "very beautiful person."
那應該是VBP了
I guess that'd be V.B.P.
但是  感謝
But um, ah, thank you!
歡迎  我是弗雷迪·馬克斯
Welcome, everyone! I'm Freddie Marks,
擔任導演  還有你們都認識的
the director,and you all know, heh,
流行歌手  裏德·韋斯特
pop sensation Reed West.
嗨  很高興來到這裏
Hi, it's lovely to be here.
我在油管上發現了裏德
I discovered Reed on YouTube,
現在我希望能找到一個全新的明星
and now I'm hoping to find a brand new star
就在這兒  就在這間屋子裏
right here in this very room.
哈珀和裏德唱了一首浪漫的二重唱
Harper sang a romantic duet with Reed.
下一個會是你嗎
Will you be next?
試鏡將明天早上舉行
Ah, now, auditions will be held tomorrow morning.
之後準備好的節目將在貴賓們留在這裏的
and the show will premiere on the very last night
最後一個晚上首演
of your VIP stay,
所以對於那些通過試鏡的人來說
so this is gonna be a fast-paced,
這將是一場快節奏  讓人興奮的冒險
exciting adventure for all those who make the cast,
尤其是那一位非常幸運的年輕女士
especially one very lucky young lady.
最好的部分是
And the best part?
如果我們的灰姑娘打動了斯裏克軌道唱片公司的主管
If our Cinderella impresses the Slick Tracks record execs,
她當場就可以簽約
she'll be signed on the spot.
沒錯  聽著不錯吧
Yeah, how about that?
好了  祝大家好運
All right, so good luck, everybody,
-明天早上見  -謝謝
- and we'll see you all in the morning. - Thank you.
再見
Cheers.
泰莎  醒醒
Earth to Tessa...
媽媽  媽媽
Mom? Mom?
救我  媽媽  我快要淹死了  我快要淹死了
Help. Mom, I'm drowning, I'm drowning!
-我的天  -救命
- Oh, my God. - Help!
抱歉  等一下
Sorry, give me one second.
好了  抓住這個
Okay, grab this.
她要淹死的時候太好笑了
She's so funny when she's drowning.
太棒了
It's so great.
輕點  泰莎
Gently, Tessa.
你能往我臉上抹點嗎
Will you do my face?
我抹勻了嗎
Am I getting it all?
還行  就是
Mm, yeah, just, um,
我感覺你漏了一塊  就在那兒
I think you missed a spot, just right...
-這兒嗎  -是  就那兒
- There? - Yeah, right there.
-沒別的了吧  -沒了
- Was that it?-  Oh, yeah.
我們可不想讓你曬傷
We wouldn't want you to get sunburned.
好了  你現在可以走了
Okay, good, you can go now.
好的
Okay.
噴
Spit.
因為  我們都想要一個知心好友
'Cause we all want a friend To call our own
有時候  天會變得很冷
These days get Mighty cold sometime
每當這時  只需閉上眼睛
So I guess I'll just make this wish
許下心願
And close my eyes
我向星星許願
And I'm wishing up on a star
無論你在哪裏我都會找到你
That I'll find you Wherever you are
我就是知道  那個特別的人
And I just know That special someone's
-一定就在某個地方  -很棒的歌  是吧
- Out there somewhere. - Great song, huh?
是呀  很好聽
Heh. Yes, it's beautiful.
沒有人想要孤身一人
Nobody ever wants To be alone
因為我們都想要一個朋友
'Cause we all want a friend
對了  我是喬治
Oh, I'm Georgie, by the way.
是這個節目的化妝師
I'm the makeup artist for the show.
我是泰莎  現在是個僕人  任人擺佈
Uh, I'm Tessa, currently an indentured servant.
但你也會唱歌
But you sing too.
所以我想我會閉上雙眼
So I guess I'll just make this wish
我聽見你哼歌兒了
I heard you humming.
我不會
No, um...
我的意思是  是  我喜歡音樂和舞蹈
I mean, yeah, I love music and dance,
但是  那應該是另一種生活了
but, um, maybe in another life.
只可惜  我們只能活一次
Too bad we only get one.
我只知道那個特別的人
I just know The special someone's
一定在某個地方
Out there somewhere
很高興見到你
Um, it was nice to meet you.
嘿  那是500cc的雙缸車嗎
Hey, is that a 500cc twin?
-1950年的  對吧  - 是  你說是就是吧
- 1950, right? - Yeah, if you say so.
-你能不能  -我們是舞台工作人員  不懂摩托車
-  Can you just--? Yeah, we're stagehands, not really bike people.
轉  轉  好的  轉彎
Turn, turn. All right, turn.
天哪  這是藍比尼最早的作品之一
Wow, that's one of Lambini's very first
真正的運動型雙V引擎
real sporting V-twin engines.
她  她真漂亮
She's-- She's beautiful.
你知不知道
You have any idea
這個運動型的東西為什麼發動不了
why one of these sporting things won't start?
這樣吧  我非常願意找出原因
You know what, I'd love to figure it out.
我可以借用一下嗎
Hey, can I borrow those?
我的褲子
My pants?
是  你的工作服
Yeah, your overalls.
-可以  當然可以  -謝謝
- Yeah-- I mean, yeah. -Thanks.
好了嗎
Yeah?
發動試試
Start 'er up.
太棒了
Hell yeah.
幹得好  泰莎
Oh, nice work, Tessa.
他們修好了摩托
Oh, they got the bike started.
我要在那兒就好了  你可以送我
I wish I was there. You could give me a ride.
定位器剛剛關了
Uh, yeah, the alignment was just off.
兩個氣缸應該一起運行才對
The two cylinders kind of needed to run as one,
-但現在都好了  -好的  太厲害了
-but it's all good now. -All right, brilliant.
謝謝  夥計
Thanks, mate.
夥計
Mate.
小德德
Reedsy-boo...
我能講完我的故事嗎
Can I finish my story?
我和基姆和帕裏斯一起吃午飯
I have lunch with Kim and Paris.
好  當然
Uh, yeah, sure, sure.
太謝謝你們了  弗雷迪會掩護你們的
Guys, thanks so much. Freddie'll cover you.
好的  愚蠢
Okay. Stupid.
不好
Oh, no.
我得走了  夥計們  等會兒見
Um, I gotta go, guys, but I'll see you later.
摩托有什麼問題隨時告訴我  好嗎
Let me know how the bike goes, 'kay?
謝謝
Thanks.
有些日子  我工作很努力
Some days I've worked so hard,
身體酸痛
my body aches
就像一個老太婆那樣
like that of an old woman.
我的臉上  全都是灰
My face is covered in... cinders.
我的腳
My feet--
畢加索  你能在線裏面塗色嗎
Hey, Picasso, can you color inside the lines?
穩點行嗎
Could you hold still？
下一個是我
Me next!
好了  閃閃
All right, Sparkles,
有一個非常重要的問題  我需要你的建議
I need your opinion on a very important subject.
你覺得呢
What do you think?
糖果色
Candy Yum-yum?
還是橙紅色
Or Lady Danger?
你個淘氣鬼
Ah, you rascal, you.
好吧  那就橙紅色
All right, Lady Danger it is.
泰莎  救救閃閃
Tessa! Save Sparkles!
閃閃溺水了
Sparkles is drowning!
她快要淹死了  她快要淹死了
She's drowning! She's drowning!
別用太多護理品  泰莎
Don't use too much product,Tessa.
要吹得蓬鬆  但又不能顯得做作
Fluffy, but not pretentious.
我能要一份
Hi. Can I...?
-給你  -謝謝
- There you go. - Thank you.
泰莎  過來坐
Hey, Tessa, come on over.
艾迪
Eddie...
-我來幫你  -你們好
- Let me get this for you. - Hey, guys.
謝謝
Thank you very much.
天哪  他們真厲害
My God, they're amazing.
我想你應該聽說過
I guess you would hear
最有才的人才能出現在這裏
The best talent makes beds in hall's trash.
泰莎  一起來
Come on, Tessa.
-跳舞去  快來  -去吧去吧
- Let's go dance, come on. - Go! Go!
泰莎  不錯啊
Wow, Tessa!
太厲害了 來   再給我們露一手
That's crazy, girl. Come on, show us some more moves.
讓我們看看你的動作
Come on, show us your moves!
-到你了  喬琪  -別這樣
- Now it's your turn, Georgie. - Don't do it.
用你的雙腳起舞
Get up on your feet
沉醉在節奏中
And get down to the beat
來吧  讓我們浸沒在喧囂中
Come on, let's live it loud
來吧來吧  就從現在開始
Come on Come on, come on now
穿好你的舞鞋
Put on your dancing shoes
我們別無所有
We got nothing to lose
衝破束縛  正是時機
Break all the locks Now's your chance
打破框架  揮舞雙手
Get out of the box And wave your hands
每個人都要縱情起舞
Everybody's got to move
你為什麼不跳  來吧  好嗎
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
工作結束  理應放鬆
Time to play When work is through, yeah
別找借口了  來吧  好嗎
There's no excuse Come on, do you
我們要拋卻規則
We're shakin' off the rules
隨心所欲
And makin' our own rules
衝破束縛  正是時機
Break all the locks Now's your chance
打破框架  揮舞雙手
Get out of the box And wave your hands
每個人都要縱情起舞
Everybody's got to move
你為什麼不跳  來吧  好嗎
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
工作結束  理應放鬆
Time to play When work is through, yeah
你為什麼不跳  來吧  好嗎
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
來吧好嗎
Everyone, do you
每個人都要縱情歌舞
Everybody, keep on dancing
來吧好嗎
Everyone, do you
好嗎
Do you
縱情歌舞
Keep on dancing
別找借口了  來吧  好嗎
There's no excuse Come on, do you
來吧好嗎
Hey, hey, hey Do you
好嗎
Ha, do you
來吧  好嗎  好嗎
Come on, do you Do you
別找借口了  來吧  好嗎
What's your excuse? Come on, do you
好嗎
Do you
好嗎  好嗎
Do you, do you
別找借口了  來吧  好嗎
There's no excuse Come on, do you, oh yeah
都給我回去工作  快走
Get back to work! Come on!
你為什麼不參加音樂劇的試鏡
Why are you not auditioning for the musical?
謝謝你  喬琪  但是我的繼母
Thanks, Georgie, but my stepmother
永遠都不會同意我去試鏡的
would never ever allow me to audition.
我有個主意
That's it!
什麼
What?
變裝試鏡
Audition in disguise.
我知道  我知道你很擅長
Okay, I'm sure-- I'm sure you're great with makeup
用刷子之類的化妝  但我覺得
and with brushes and stuff, but I doubt it could...
把嘴撅起來
Pout for me.
真要這樣嗎  我不太確定
I'm not so sure about this.
別說話
Shush, shush and shush.
好了  我們開始吧
Yeah, let's begin.
門未上鎖  我們破門而入
Kick in the door no locks
趴在地上  我們不會報警
Get on the floor We no call the cops
女士們先生們  你們應該清楚
Ladies and gentlemen You should know
這是砸場子  我們要做主角
This is a stick-up We steal the show
曾經的表演者  快跑吧
Now run Tiggy run run Tiggy run run
聽到動靜就快跑吧
Hearing that bum bum When it come come
我們身上的光芒足以使燈光黯然失色
Lights in a bomb When we in the room
致命一擊
Bull's-eye.
有人為錢而來
One for the money
我們卻會讓你失控
We gonna make you Lose control
喬琪  她是誰
Oh, hey, Georgie, who's your friend?
-咱倆認識啊  -她是位客人  艾迪
- You know who I am. - She's a guest, Eddie.
是位客人
She's a guest.
如果你需要什麼  只管吩咐我們
If you need anything, you just, you let us know.
我可以幫你  幫你打掃房間
I can sweep. Sweep your room.
打掃  打掃房間
Sweep, sweep rooms.
我還穿過他的工作服呢  他都沒認出我
He didn't recognize me and I've worn his coveralls.
好吧  我不知道你在說什麼
Okay, I don't know what that means,
但我確定了一點  你一定得去試鏡
but I feel vindicated. Now you have to audition.
喬琪  聽著  你的化妝刷
Georgie, look, your makeup brushes
就像魔杖一樣神奇  但我不能去試鏡
are like magic wands, but I can't do this.
我的家人一下子就會認出我的聲音
My family will recognize my voice immediately.
那就偽裝一下  我們到了
Then disguise it. Here we are.
不應該是
It's not like,
我是奧林匹亞
"I'm Olympia."
我在這裏
"I'm here."
我是你的
"I'm yours."
好吧  我要過去了
Okay, I'm going.
好
Okay.
-我真的要去了  -好的  去吧
- I'm gonna do this. - Okay, go.
好的  我這就要去了
Okay, I'm gonna go.
-去吧  -好
- Just go.- Okay.
你根本沒在聽我說話
You're not listening to me.
珍妮特  你看起來不錯
Wow, Janet, you look great.
別擔心  別人根本不會注意到
And don't worry, no one will even notice
你額頭漲出的青筋
that huge vein bulging out of your forehead.
年輕人  你是VIP客人嗎
Young lady, are you a VIP guest?
我沒在吃早午餐的時候看到過你
I didn't see you at the brunch.
電車壞了
Um, the trolley broke.
電車
The trolley?
是的  很遺憾電車壞了
Yes. But it's a bloody shame the trolley broke.
我肯定在哪兒見過你
I know you from somewhere.
不可能
No, um...
我沒
Uh, I don't--
我覺得不可能
I don't think so.
在尼德邁耶  猶太少年成人禮上見過嗎
The Niedermeyer Bar Mitzvah?
一起聽過猶太歌
Did we Hava Nagila?
女士  我未曾有此殊榮
I don't think I had that pleasure, ma'am.
你確實沒這等福分
Eh. You didn't have that pleasure.
那就是在費城的國際狗狗展示會上
The National Dog Show in Philly?
恐怕不是  我喜歡貓
Afraid not. Um, I'm a cat person.
-甚至你身上的味道我都覺得熟悉  -是香草味
- You even smell familiar. - It's vanilla.
是我體香劑的味道  這種味道在倫敦特別流行
It's my deodorant. It's all the rage in London.
英格蘭
England.
很有意思
Very interesting.
行吧
All right.
好的
Yes.
我盯上你了
I've got my eyes on you.
沒有必要  隨便你
Oh, that won't be necessary, it's okay.
再見
Cheers!
天祐女王 遠在倫敦的女王陛下
God save the queen. In London.
就是我家鄉的那個倫敦
Where I'm from.
隨便吧  奧林匹亞
Whatever. All right, Olympia...
太險了
Oh, that was close.
我知道大雨即將落下
I know the rain is falling
不必滿面愁容
Don't look so sad about it
我知道也許會有點痛
I know it hurts a little
你想要高聲呼喊
You want to scream And shout it
我有挽救方法
I got the remedy
就跟著節奏一遍一遍盡情搖擺
So let the rhythm take you Over and over
結尾會特別精彩
She has a big finish!
我知道你萬分沮喪
I know you're down
我來讓你展開笑顏
Let me picking you up
我知道你很堅強
I know you're strong
我知道你很堅韌
I know you're tough
你想坐在一旁
You want to sit
但你需要舞動
You need to move
就到這裏吧  謝謝你
Okay, thank you, dear. Next!
請大點聲
A little louder, please.
下一位
Next!
見證奇跡的時刻到了
Prepare to be amazed.
我說我們出發吧  我將帶你前往巔峰
I said let's go, go Take it to the top now
我們態度強硬  永不止步
Goin' hard and we're Never gonna stop now
想像出我們和諧而又都在閃耀的圖景
Picture us All a-rhyme and glow
但我們一刻都不能等了
But we cannot wait a second Baby no
所以我穿著細高跟  穿上臍裝
So walkin' in stilettos In my midriff, midriff
操縱變速桿  全速前進
Pedal to the metal in My stick shift, stick shift
拼盡全力  吸引所有人的目光
Sit and rob attention,like you on a mission
是時候實現一些我清單上的願望了
About to check Some shit off my wish list
我要開始了  沒人能阻擋我
Gonna set it up And no one can stop me
我要開始了  等著瞧吧
I'm gonna turn it up Go ahead and watch me
停  停  快停下來
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
放在那裏就行了  別的搬走
Yeah, get right up there. Clear it out.
這就很完美了  這裏要打光
That'll look perfect. There should be lighting right there.
開始吧
Okay, go ahead.
你們喜歡聽什麼
What's doth ye lads fancy?
我們想聽什麼   弗雷迪
What do we doth fancy, Freddie?
親愛的  你來之前應該有所準備
You're supposed to come prepared, sweetie.
是的
Right.
我只是  等一下
I just-- Just one second.
沒有人願意孤身一人
Nobody ever Wants to be alone
因為我們都想要一個知心好友
'Cause we all want a friend To call our own
有時候  天會變得很冷
These days get mighty cold Sometimes
每當這時  只需閉上眼睛  許下心願
So I guess I'll just make This wish and close my eyes
這世上沒有我不能涉足之處
There is no place That I won't go
為了尋求真愛  我願上刀山
Because for love I will search high
也願下火海
And I'll search low
不論付出什麼代價  我願意一試
All things worth having Takes a risk
只要有機會
If I got one shot
希望我不會錯過
I hope that I don't miss
我對著星星許願
And I'm wishin' Upon a star
無論你在世界上的哪個角落  我都會找到你
That I'll find you Wherever you are
我知道  屬於我的那個他就在某個地方
And I just know that special Someone's out there somewhere
很普通
Well, it's pretty average.
你叫什麼名字
What's your name?
-灰姑娘  -灰姑娘
- Um, Cinderella. - Cinderella.
挺諷刺
Oh. Ironic.
一點點
Just a bit.
我喜歡你的上衣
I like your top.
我有一條圖案一樣的短褲
I've got a pair of boxers like those.
倫敦萬歲
Go London.
-愛國主義  你懂的  -懂
- Patriotic, you know. - Yeah, heh.
你到底是哪裏人
Where about you from?
我有點辨別不出你的口音
I can't quite find your accent.
你聽不出來嗎
Oh, you can't?
真奇怪
That's odd.
我是從  一個小村莊來的
I'm from-- It's a small farming village.
在倫敦北部
It's just north of London.
名字是
It's called, um...
約克郡布丁縣
It's called Yorkshire Puddingshire.
-約克布丁郡  -約克郡布丁縣
York Puddingshire? York-- Yorkshire.
約克郡布丁縣  這樣啊
Yorkshire Puddingshire, oh.
-是的  -好吧
- Yes - Okay.
是挨著
Oh, is that near...?
沒錯
Y-- Uh-huh.
就在
It's-- It's right--
就在霍格沃茨郡邊上
It's right near Ho-- Hogwarts shire.
-霍格沃茨郡  弗萊迪  -是的
- Hogwarts shire, Freddie. - Yes.
我就知道
I knew it.
好吧
Yeah. Okay.
約克郡布丁縣女孩  讓我看看你跳舞跳得怎麼樣
Well, Yorkshire Puddingshire, let me see if you can move.
你想讓我跳舞
You want me to dance?
是的  我非常想看你跳舞
Yeah, I'd love you to dance.
告訴我  你喜歡我的舞步嗎
Tell me, baby Did you like the way I move?
換上你的舞鞋
Come on, Get your dancer on
你能盡享歡樂
You can have as much fun As you can possibly have
別忘了穿褲子
With your pants on
當我望進你的雙眼
When I look in your eyes
他們告訴我  冷靜
They saying chillax
我肯定  有個魔鬼住在那裏
I bet you There's a devil inside
我們彼此相連
Hookin' and playin', baby
我不想失控
I hate to lose
所以在舞池中展示給我看吧
So show me On the dance floor
我看得出你很在行
I can see you got game
我也是行家
Well, I got game
你最好給我一手  來吧
You better show me By your game, come on
讓我們開始吧
Let's get this game on
來吧  寶貝
Come on, babe
讓我們開始吧
Let's get this game on
是誰點燃了愛的火花
Who can start a fire?
就是這樣的火花
The fire be like that
你準備好了嗎  準備好什麼
Are you ready? For what?
-你會跳薩爾薩舞嗎  -一點都不會
- Can you salsa? Oh. - Not at all.
-接住我  -接住你
- Catch me. - Catch you?
遊戲人間嘛  你懂的  這沒關係
Everything is playing You know, it's all right
如果咱們只是玩玩
If you're playing With me now, oh yeah
-她是誰  -不好說
- Who the hell is she? - Uh, it's hard to say.
為什麼她有跳舞的機會
Why does she get to dance?
不好說  她是個冒牌貨
Hard to say? She's an imposter!
她都沒出席早午餐聚會
She wasn't even at the kickoff brunch!
她現在出現了啊
Well, she's here now.
很抱歉  我得走了
I'm so sorry, I have to go.
什麼  不  等一下  你很厲害  等一下
What? No, wait, you're amazing. Wait.
抓住她  她冒充VIP
Arrest that girl! She's impersonating a VIP!
抓住那個女孩
Arrest that girl!
我猜大概童話大神顯靈了
Well, I guess the fairy tale gods have spoken.
你們倆一起跳舞的時候
The way you two danced together...
就像童話成真了
It was like a fairy tale.
我肯定  他會選你
I bet he's gonna pick you.
這不重要了  你看到我繼母的嘴臉了
It doesn't matter. You saw Divine.
她能分分鐘讓我失去資格
She'd get me disqualified in a heartbeat.
我們會想出一個假名字  一切都會很順利的
We'll come up with a fake name and it'll all work out.
喬琪  我很抱歉
Georgie, I'm really sorry.
我真的  很感激你
I really-- I really appreciate everything
感激你為我所做的一切  但是
you've done for me, but...
我覺得是時候回到現實了
I think it's time for me to get back to my real life.
但還是謝謝你
But thank you.
坐直了  坐直了
Oh-oh, sit up straight. Sit up straight.
我想
Well, I'd just like to start off by saying
向大家道謝開始
thank you very much to everyone here
謝謝你們參加今天的試鏡
for auditioning today.
我們即將張貼配角名單
We're posting a cast list soon of the secondary roles,
但是
but...
我找到我的灰姑娘了
I found my Cinderella.
現在我只需要在人群中真的找出她
Well, now I just need to actually find her, heh.
這位神秘的灰姑娘
Our mystery Cinderella,
她今天在試鏡的時候遺失了一隻舞鞋
she lost her dance shoe today at the audition.
是一隻很特別的鞋子
It's a very special shoe.
如果你有與之配對的鞋
Uh, if you're the owner of that matching shoe,
請在明天午夜前來找我
then please come forward by midnight tomorrow...
這個角色就是你的了
and the role is yours.
謝謝大家
Thank you.
姑娘們  姑娘們  讓開  別擋路
Girls! Girls! Out of my way! Out of my way!
跟我走  跟上跟上
Excuse me! Follow me! Try to keep up! Try to keep up!
都讓開  我要過來了
Clear the road! Coming through!
-這個嗎  -不是
- This one? - Nope.
-這個呢  這個呢  -不是  還不是
- This one? This one? - Nope. Nope.
-是這個嗎  -不是
- This one? - Nope.
-這個呢  -我不確定
- This one? - I'm not sure!
使勁想  奧林匹亞
Think, Olympia.
調動起你那所剩不多的腦細胞
Round up every last little brain cell that's in there.
早上好
Good morning.
-這個嗎  這個呢  -不是  也不是
This one? This one? Nope. Nope.
這個  等等  就是它
This-- Wait. Yes.
這個  這個就是那個鞋花  就是那個
That's-- That's the shoe flower, that's the one.
泰莎
Oh. Tessa...
你得把這朵花畫在這個鞋子上
You need to paint that flower on this shoe.
沒什麼意義吧
Um, there's no point,
因為如果他有相對應的另一隻運動鞋  那麼
because if he has the matching sneaker, then--
其他人都不知道這個手繪花
Nobody else knows about the hand-painted flower.
他必須在午夜前挑選一個人
He has to pick somebody by midnight.
去  去  去
Go! Go! Go!
你猜怎麼著  《放鬆》剛剛進了公告牌排行榜最熱100
Guess what? "Get Loose" just made the Billboard Hot 100!
這也太快了
Wow, that was fast.
看  我告訴過你  和哈珀合作二重唱會給你的事業鑲金的
See, I told you duet with Harper would be gold for your career.
如果有人感興趣
Uh, if anybody's interested,
配角選角名單剛剛張貼在後台了
the supporting cast list has just been posted backstage.
來吧  裏德  我們走吧
Come on, Reed, let's go!
好吧  我盡力了  但我真的不認為這會有效果
Okay, I tried, but I just really don't think this is gonna work.
怎麼了  是有人死了嗎
What happened? Did someone die?
比這更糟  碧安卡要扮演僊女教母
Worse! Bianca got cast as Fairy Godmother.
珍妮特扮演惡毒的繼母
Janet's the Evil Stepmother,
而我們要演的卻是
and all we get to play is the...
醜陋的繼姐  醜陋的繼姐
Ugly Stepsisters! Ugly Stepsisters!
他們怎麼可以認為  我們應該飾演
How could they possibly think that we should play
那種卑鄙  又超級自私的女孩
those mean, horrible self-absorbed girls?!
天啊  這簡直符合想像  不是嗎
Gosh, it just boggles the imagination, doesn't it?
終於搞定了
Finally.
什麼  你是用腳趾頭畫的嗎
What, did you paint it with your toes?
像往常一樣  我會處理好一切的
As usual, I'll take care of things.
對嗎  姑娘們
Right, girls?
你沒聽見嗎
Uh, hello?
門鈴響了
Doorbell.
奧林匹亞  坐直
Olympia, sit up straight.
雅典娜  別擺出一副沮喪的表情
Athena, stop looking so depressed.
信是裏德·韋斯特的
It's from Reed West.
裏德·韋斯特希望陪同見面的人有
"Reed West requests the company of..."
不
No!
他寫了什麼  發生什麼了
What is it? What's wrong?
你
You!
他為什麼想見你
Why does he want to see you?!
什麼
What?
我看見你在裏德說話的時候
I saw you at Reed's announcement
眼睛都黏在他身上了
making gooey eyes at him.
不  這  這太荒
No, it's-- That's ridic--
你為了他去修眉毛了  是不是
You plucked your eyebrows for him, didn't you?
不  我沒有  我沒有  只是
No, I didn't, I didn't. It's just--
這只是一些  一個大誤會
It's just some-- A big misunderstanding.
這只是個愚蠢的錯誤  這樣  我們會弄明白的  好嗎
It's just a silly mistake. Well, we'll find out, shall we?
跟我來
Come with me!
姑娘們  姑娘們  我們要走了
Girls! Girls! We're leaving!
看這裏  凝視這裏
See there, staring here
是的  我們要搞清楚這件事的真相
Yeah, we're gonna get to the bottom of this
現在  小姑娘  如果你把我家女孩們的事搞砸了
right now, little missy, and if you screw things up for my girls--
姑娘們  快點跟上
Girls, try to keep up.
裏德  裏德·韋斯特
Oh, Reed. Reed West.
我把泰莎帶來了  你想見她嗎
I have Tessa here. You wanted to see her?
等一下
Oh, hang on a sec.
是的  我們一直在找你
Oh, yes, we've been trying to track you down.
你在找我
You have?
你為什麼想要想見她
Uh, why would you want to see her?
我  我只是需要你的幫助
Well, I-- I just need your help.
-是嗎  -演出差不多就要靠它了
- You do? - The show kinda depends on it.
是嗎
It does?
機修工說
The mechanic said
昨天是你發動了摩托車
you were the one who got her started yesterday.
對  對  是我
Yeah. Yeah. I did.
很抱歉  誤認為你是個男生
I'm sorry for mistaking you for a dude.
我的錯
It's my bad.
沒關係  我只是
It's okay, I'm just--
我很高興現在一切都明瞭了
I'm just glad everything's all cleared up now.
好吧  還有一個問題
Right, well, there's a--
車一直發出一種輕微的噪聲
There's like a little clunking noise
聲音是從  從
coming from the-- From, uh--
摩托車上發出來的
Uh, from the motorcycle.
-摩托的聲音  -對
- From the bike. - Yeah.
你能描述一下嗎
Um, could you describe the clunking?
知道了  是那種快速的突突聲嗎
Okay. Is it like a fast tk-tk?
有點像  它開始是像
Kind of. Well, it starts off--
感覺聲音不斷增強
It starts off like it's building.
好，那就是
Okay. So like "b-b-b-b-b" tk, tk?
不  更像
No, it's more like
像火車一樣
Like a train?
我不知道那是什麼火車  但是  是這樣的
I don't know what trains you've heard, but yeah,
關掉就沒聲兒了  如果我試著再發動
it cuts out, and if I try and do it again,
它就繼續  突  突  突  突  突
it goes, tk, tk, tk, tk, tk, tk.
好了  我知道問題在哪兒了
Um, yeah, I think I know it.
好吧  能修好就修好
Well, we just need to get it fixed if we can,
不然的話灰姑娘就沒有南瓜車了
otherwise Cinderella won't have a pumpkin carriage.
我可以試試
I can try.
等等  等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
如果我讓我親愛的泰莎為你做這件事
If I let my darling Tessa do this for you,
你必須為我做點什麼
you have to do something for me.
你必須讓我富有才華的女兒們再次試鏡
You have to let my talented daughters audition again.
她們第一次試鏡遇到了些小問題
They had an eentsy problem the first time.
順便說一句
By the way,
準備好  她們會驚艷到你的
prepare to have your mind blown.
好  成交
Yeah, deal.
來吧  姑娘們  我們要去練習了
Come on, girls, we have to practice!
再見
Bye.
弗雷迪  我們能帶泰莎去道具間嗎
Uh, Freddie, can we set Tessa up in the prop room, please?
不是
It's not--
我發誓  沒看上去的那麼糟
It's not as bad as it looks, I swear, heh.
跟我剛才看到的混亂一比  不值一提
Well, this is nothing compared to the hot mess I just saw, heh.
當然  我不小心聽到了一點
I'm sure, I kind of overheard a little bit.
好的  這些是我需要你拿來的部件
Okay, so these are the parts that I need you to get,
這樣我就可以修好你的南瓜車了
so that I can fix your pumpkin carriage.
你是從哪裏學會做這些的
Where did you learn to do all this?
我爸爸是賽車手
Um, my dad was a racecar driver.
是啊
Yeah.
他有自己的修理店
He had his own repair shop,
所以基本上是
so I was basically
在我能走路之前  就和車打交道
working on cars before I could walk.
你爸爸現在還賽車嗎
Is your dad still racing cars now?
要是這樣就好了
Um, I hope so.
他去世了
In heaven.
你能把9/16英吋扳手遞給我嗎
Could you pass me the 9/16th spanner?
-不能  -就是扳鉗
- No. - Oh, the wrench.
不  我不知道是哪一個
No, I don't know what that one is.
那個小的  銀色的
The small, silver thing, r--
-是這個  -對
-This one? -Mm-hm.
這個小的銀色工具  就是這個
Small silver thing here. Right there.
-你剛開始就該這麼說  -謝謝
- You should've just said that. - Thanks, heh.
你爸爸也讓小泰莎駕駛賽車嗎
So did your dad let Baby Tessa drive racecars too?
沒有
No.
沒有  我到5歲才能開
No, I had to wait till I was about 5 for that.
好吧  非常明智
Ha, ha. All right, wise to wait.
你做到了  寶貝
You did it, babe!
演出門票售罄了  度假區也是
The show sold out. The resort too.
-爸爸高興極了  -  太好了
- Heh, Dad's thrilled. - Oh, that's great.
弗雷迪說你還沒有選好女主角
Freddie says you haven't cast Cinderella yet?
是啊  還沒有
No, not yet.
但是我們已經有了能接下角色的人選
But there's someone we're hoping's gonna accept it.
那就加油啊  大帥哥
Then make it happen, hot stuff.
好了  我要起飛了
Anyway, gotta fly.
發生了很多事
a lot goin' on.
沒關係
It's okay.
如果這個女孩再不出現  我就有麻煩了
I'm in trouble if this girl doesn't show.
你真的認為你的神秘女孩那麼好嗎
You really think your mystery girl's that good?
那當然
Oh, definitely.
但皇家度假區希望我們今天就能完成選角
But Royal Resorts want us to complete casting today.
如果神秘女孩不站出來
And if mystery girl doesn't come forward,
我們也必須挑選其他人
then we have to pick someone else.
我喜歡和你一起待著
I like spending time with you.
如果你明天能見我  我也會很高興的
I'd really like it if you'd meet me tomorrow,
還有  也許
and maybe, uh,
我能拿著你的扳鉗
well, you'd let me hold your spanner.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我以為他是那種
I thought he was going to be like,
身材很好  人很狂妄的類型  但是
all abs and attitude, but...
他  他真是太貼心了
he's-- He's so sweet.
這裏有人墜入愛河了
Heh, someone's crushing hard.
算了吧  他在和一位漂亮又有名的女繼承人約會
Oh, please, he's dating a gorgeous celebrity heiress.
她連給你提鞋的資格都沒有
Who can't possibly hold a candle to you.
她不需要這樣做  有人會幫她做
She doesn't have to, she has people for that.
沒關係  事情本來就是這樣
It's okay, it's just the way things are.
我希望
I wish...
什麼
What?
你爸爸
Your dad.
他實現了他的夢想  對吧
He made his dreams come true, right?
是啊
Yeah.
他應該也希望你實現夢想吧
Wouldn't he want you to do the same?
我只是不想看到
I just hate to see
完美的夢想被白白浪費
perfectly good dreams go to waste.
好了  爸爸
Okay, Dad,
我會勇敢起來
I'll be brave.
快來
Come on!
需要花多長時間
How much longer is this gonna take?
我不知道
I don't know.
-我不知道  -好的
- I don't know. - All right.
看  她不來了  我們可以再選一個人了嗎
Look, she's not coming. Can we just pick someone?
不  還沒到午夜
No, it's not midnight yet.
再等幾分鐘
Just a few more minutes.
停下
Stop it!
太煩人了
So annoying.
真是服了
Unbelievable.
裏德  如果我們再不挑人
Reed, if we don't pick someone,
他們會取消我們的演出
they'll cancel my show.
拜託了
Please?
好吧
All right.
我來得太晚了嗎
Am I too late?
-就是她  對吧  -是
- It's her, right? - Heh, yeah.
-你好  -你好
- Hello.  -Hello.
櫻花是我媽媽最喜歡的花
Cherry blossoms were me mum's favorite flowers.
你為什麼跑了
Why did you run?
我很猶豫到底要不要來試鏡
I wasn't sure I should've auditioned at all.
哦
Oh.
那你改變主意了嗎
Well, you've changed your mind?
你要當我的灰姑娘嗎
All right, you'll be my Cinderella?
嗯
Yes.
等一下
Hold on a second!
等一等
Wait one minute!
等等  等等  我有話要說
Hold on! Hold on! I have something to say!
這個女孩
This girl,
我敢打賭她不是一名合法的客人
I bet she's not even a legitimate guest.
什麼  那太荒謬了
What? That's absurd.
哦  太荒謬了
Oh, absurd!
你叫什麼名字
Well, what's your name?
我的名字
My name?
沒錯
Hm, yes.
對啊  因為每個人
Right, because everyone--
每個人都有名字  對吧
Everyone has a name, right?
快說
Spit it out.
名字
The-- See, the name
我媽媽給我起的名字是
that my mother gave me was...
貝拉
Bella!
Bella.
-貝拉·貝金漢姆  -貝拉·斯諾
- Bella Buckingham. - Bella Snow!
- Bella Buckingham？  - Bella Snow！
是貝拉·貝金漢姆·斯諾
It's Bella Buckingham Snow.
簡稱貝拉·斯諾
Bel-- Bella Snow, for short.
很高興見到你
It's good to see you!
我剛才還去了你媽媽的城堡
I was just at your mom's castle.
在  在約克郡布丁縣  多可愛啊
In-in Yorkshire Puddingshire, how lovely, heh!
是的  貝拉·斯諾  會員  她是合法的
Yep, Bella Snow, VIP. She's legit.
好的  好的  好的
Okay, all right. All right.
我盯上你了
I'm on to you!
你和你的蠢運動鞋
You and your silly sneakers
最好都小心點
had better watch your step!
好了  看劇本
Okay then, read this,
檢查各項環節  熟悉作息安排
check out the links, learn the routines,
早上開始排練
start rehearsal in the morning.
好的
All right, heh.
不行  你不能喝碳酸飲料
No! No carbs for you!
你太胖了
You're getting too fat.
這是你要的平板電腦
Here's the tablet you requested.
好的  坐下  我想讓你搜點東西
All right. Sit down, I want you to Google something.
好   你想讓我搜什麼
Okay, what do you want me to Google?
搜一下  "貝拉·斯諾"
Google "Bella Snow."
-斯諾  -貝拉·斯諾
- Snow. - Bella Snow.
斯諾[雪]  就是會從天上飄下來的東西
Snow, like the stuff that falls from the sky.
B-E-L-  電腦給我
B-E-L-- Just give that to me.
讓我來搜  你太慢了
Let me do it. You're so slow.
你來搜  她太慢了
You do it. She's too slow.
好了
Okay...
好了  這裏有一個
Okay, here's one.
貝拉·斯諾
Bella Snow,
一名新澤西的牙科醫生
a dentist in New Jersey.
那不是她
That's not her.
那個女孩可沒那麼聰明
That girl is as brainless as they come.
好吧  我找到一個英國人叫貝拉·斯諾
Okay, I found a British Bella Snow,
她一百年前就去世了
who died a hundred years ago.
沒用的  她根本就不存在
This is pointless. She doesn't exist!
我就知道  她是個冒牌貨
I knew it! She's an imposter!
我要你在排練結束後跟著她
I want you to follow her after rehearsal,
弄清楚她是誰
and find out who she is.
我
Me?
-我也要去  -我可以去嗎
- I will go, too.  - Can I go?
噓  噓
Shh! Shh!
噓
Shh!
我去確認一下廚師是否清楚
I'm gonna go make sure the chef
你們的晚餐要求
has your suggestions for dinner.
好吧  我跟你說
Oh, all right. And you know,
我今天想坐在小屋旁的噴霧站
I want the spritzing station by the cabana today.
-知道了  -我喜歡噴霧的感覺
-Got it. -I love to be spritzed.
到時候就跟著你的感覺走
Just go with what you're feeling at the time.
不要事先計劃好
And don't decide beforehand.
就跟著那一瞬間的感覺走  好嗎
Just let it be whatever you're feeling in the moment, okay?
-可以嗎  -好
- Yeah? - Cool.
太好了  你來了
Oh, good, you're here.
好了  我們想來一首灰姑娘的開場曲
Okay, so, um, we wanna do Cinderella's opening song.
你準備好了  對吧
You're ready, right?
好的  各位  讓我們給她留一些空間
Okay, great, let's give her some space, folks.
這首歌講述的是一個生活艱難的女孩
Right, the song's about a girl who lives a difficult life,
她總是失敗
filled with loss,
難以找尋勇氣去追逐她的夢想
who struggles to find the courage to go after her dreams.
試著去體會一下那種感覺  好嗎
Try to imagine what that might be like, okay?
我會的
I can try.
好了  大家各就各位
Okay, places, everybody.
我是這樣一個人
I've never been one
不曾踏出自己的舒適圈
To step out of My comfort zone
每次努力時
Whenever I try
都擔心自己止步不前
I'm afraid to just let go
我是這樣一個人
I've never been one
不曾掙脫束縛自由翱翔
To break free
因為我總是在意他人的目光
'Cause I've always cared What everyone thinks Of me
我不知道我為什麼逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我為什麼隱藏
Don't know why I hide
不讓他人知曉自己真實的內心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不知道我為什麼害怕
Don't know why I'm scared
當我站立於此
Just to take a chance
只能放手一搏
When I'm just standing here
如同飛鳥  我自由飛翔
Like a bird I'm free to fly
張開雙翼  尋找生命的意義
Spread my wings And find my life
如同飛鳥  我飛入高空
Like a bird I'm up so high
飛出牢籠  是時候大放異彩
Out of the cage It's my time to shine
如同飛鳥  我自由飛翔
Like a bird I'm free to fly
所以告訴我  告訴我
So tell me, tell me
我為什麼要逃避
Why don't I?
我們終於找到合適的女主了
We definitely found our girl.
好了
Okay.
舉起手臂  向上  向上  向上
Arms up. Up, up, up.
抱歉
Sorry.
你的腰細得就跟小蜂鳥一樣
You got a waist like a little hummingbird.
再見
Cheers.
貝拉
Bella.
喬吉
Georgie.
看看你  跟公主一樣
Oh, look at you, all princessy!
我第一次覺得
For the first time, I feel like...
也許我能做到  真的能做到
maybe I can do this. Like, for real.
你好
Hi!
-過來  -天啊
- Come on! - Ugh, my God,
我的姐姐們就在外面等著我
my stepsisters are waiting to follow me outside.
我們從後面走  她們不會想到的
We'll go out the back. They won't expect it.
-你確定嗎  -那當然了
- You sure? - Mm-hm.
好吧  那我走了  拜
Okay. I'm gonna go. Bye. Okay.
她去哪裏了
Where is she?
快跟上
Come on!
知道了
Okay.
-好吧  你走那邊  -好
- Okay. You go that way. - Okay.
抓到你了
Catch you.
幹嘛
What?
你是誰
Who are you?
-抓到你了  -奧林匹亞
- Catch you. - Olympia!
在  在這裏見到你真是太高興了
Oh, it's just such a-- Such a delight to see you here.
是嗎
It is?
你能不能
Would you be so kind as to
把防曬霜遞給我
pass me that suntan lotion over there too?
我們英國人  可禁不起曬
We Brits, we just crisp so easily.
能幫我下嗎  我夠不著
Oh, do you mind? I can't reach.
謝謝你
Thank you.
跟我說說吧  奧林匹亞
So tell me, Olympia,
把這些圍巾都塞進嘴裏是不是很困難
was it hard to get all those scarves in your mouth?
哦  我已經訓練好幾個星期了
Oh, I had to train my cheeks for weeks.
-是嗎  -你想看看嗎
- Did you? - Do you wanna see?
當然
Sure.
塞了好多葡萄啊
That's a lot of grapes.
你知道怎麼樣才能顯得更可愛嗎  加一些檸檬水
Do you know what would be lovely? Some lemonade.
再加點零食
Mm. And snacks.
-是的  還有零食  -我去拿
- Yes, and snacks. - I can get 'em!
-哦  你去吧  -嗯哼
- Oh, you could. - Mm-hm.
-那實在是太好了  -好的
- Oh, that's absolutely perfect. - Okay.
謝謝  我就在這裏等你
Thank you. I'll be just right here waiting,
就在這裏  不會走的
right here, won't move.
她人很好  又聰明
She's so nice. And smart.
只是在我幫她拿來零食之前
Oh. But then she disappeared
她就消失了
before I could give her her snacks.
你被耍了  奧林匹亞
Ugh. You got played, Olympia.
你就是嫉妒
You're just jealous
因為貝拉比你更漂亮
because Bella's head is prettier than yours.
你去哪裏了
Where have you been?
我剛去拿你們訂的衣服了
I was just picking up the dresses you ordered.
這是為化妝舞會準備的嗎
Are these for the Costume Ball?
我們要打扮成灰姑娘
We're going as Cinderellas.
嘛哩嘛哩哄
Abracadabra!
哈哈哈  那個  魔法師就是這麼說的
Heh, heh, just... that's what a magician says.
這是你的魔杖
Uh, so this is your wand.
用法很簡單  我給你演示一下
It's very simple to use. Just demonstrate for you.
基諾  你能站到灰姑娘的位置上嗎
Uh, Gino, could you step into Cinderella's position, please?
-好的  -你只需要這樣
- Yeah. - So all you do is...
轉圈
twirl.
明白了嗎
See?
很簡單的  只需要轉動手腕
Uh, it's so easy. Just a flick of the wrist.
拿好了  去感受下吧
Here, go ahead. Get a feel for it,
有任何問題  都可以跟我說
and, uh, let me know if you have any questions.
打擾一下
Sorry.
她太荒謬了吧
She's ridiculous.
你是怎麼想的  居然讓碧安卡和她的姐妹們出演
What were you thinking getting Bianca and her stepsisters in the show?
奧林匹亞  快住手  太噁心了
Olympia, stop it. Gross.
我們別無選擇
We have no choice.
會員套餐承諾她們可以出演配角
The VIP package guarantees them supporting roles.
別擔心了
Don't worry.
沒事的
It'll be fine.
我能讓每個人都有精彩的表現
I can get a great performance out of anybody.
這些翅膀太重了
These wings are so heavy.
她能演好的
She's gonna be great.
臂部有四個節拍
So it's four beats in the hips.
貝拉來了
Oh, uh, Bella's here,
那麼  我們來排練下穿鞋的戲吧
so let's rehearse the shoe-fitting scene, please.
這就是接下來的安排
Yes, that's what we're gonna do.
弗雷迪
Freddie,
你能在沒有我的情況下先排練嗎
can you run the show without me for a little bit?
啥  為什麼  你要去哪裏
What? Why? Where are you going?
修理灰姑娘的南瓜馬車
To fix Cinderella's pumpkin carriage.
沒有它就沒法演出了  對吧
Can't do the show without it, right?
我應該可以替你
I guess I'll stand in.
如果泰莎不在那裏
If Tessa's not there,
他會覺得她是個騙子或者根本就沒放在心上
he'll think she's a flake or doesn't care.
你沒法同時出現在兩個地方
You can't be in two places at once.
-帶上工作服和帽子在化妝室等我  可以嗎  -好
- Meet me in Make-up with coveralls and a cap, okay? - Okay.
-你要怎麼辦  -問得好
- How are you gonna pull this off? - Great question.
我先讓裏德開始  接著跟他說我要走了
I think I'll get Reed started, then tell him I have to go.
再回來這裏和你碰面  戴上貝拉的假髮
I'll just meet you back here for the Bella wig.
你再用你的魔力之手幫我化妝
You work your magic with your magic make-up hands.
我們能處理好的
We'll figure something out.
好了
Okay. Oh.
等一下  好了
Wait. Okay.
-你要梳下頭嗎  -不用了  就這樣
- Do you need a brush? - Oh, no, that's okay.
天吶
Oh, God.
好了
Okay.
給你
Here.
-看起來不錯  -好的
- You look good. - Okay.
好的
Okay.
謝天謝地  我以為你忘了
Oh, thank God. I thought you forgot.
不  我  只是花了點時間打扮得性感一點
No, I, uh... It just takes a little time to look this hot.
對不起
Sorry.
我拿到了你要的那些零件
I got those parts that you asked for.
-我不知道  -哇哦
- I don't know-- - Oh, wow.
太棒了
That's amazing.
我沒想到你這麼快就弄到這些零件了
I'm surprised you got these parts so quickly.
算是當明星的好處吧
Yeah, well, the perks of being a pop star.
-肯定很爽  -也不完全是
- Must be nice. - Not really.
沒有人有義務聆聽明星的煩惱
But nobody should have to listen to pop star problems.
比如說想要什麼就有什麼
Like getting everything you could want,
包括很棒的車零件
including awesome bike parts?
不完全是這樣
Not exactly.
或者說
Or, like, um...
也許不能遵從你的心聲
not being able to follow your heart, maybe.
我聽過你為音樂劇寫的那些歌
I heard those songs that you wrote for the musical.
真的很不錯
They're really good.
非常動聽
Beautiful.
真的
Really?
不是開玩笑
Honestly?
是真的
Honestly.
那才是真正的你  對吧
That's the real you, right?
弗雷迪覺得我應該繼續走現在的風格
Well, Freddie just thinks I need to stick to my brand
直到我的事業達到另一個高度
until my career reaches the next level.
然後我就可以做自己想做的了
Then I can do whatever I want.
也許弗雷迪錯了
Freddie could be wrong.
嗯  只是他從來都是對的
Yes, it's just that he's been right about everything else.
就像我說的  明星的煩惱
Mm. Like I said, pop star problems.
我會幫你保密的
Well, they're safe with me.
嗯  我相信你
Yeah, I believe they are.
-你會需要這個的  -是的
-Yeah, you're gonna need that. - Yeah.
快來
Come on!
你能快速擰緊這些螺栓
Will you just tighten these bolts really quick
並且把傳送帶安好
and, um, finish putting on the belt.
我  我馬上就回來
And I will be-- I'll be right back.
我得去檢查一些東西
I've gotta go check on some things.
你會回來嗎  你不在我可搞不定
You're gonna come back? I can't do this without you.
當然啦  我會回來的
Yes. Of course, I'll be back.
天吶
Oh, God.
-貝拉  -好了
- Bella... - There you go.
這裏應該有你的聲音
You're supposed to make a noise there.
我有錯過試穿水晶鞋嗎
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
王國中的每位少女都有機會
Every maiden in the land is granted the opportunity.
會是她嗎
Could that be her?
讓我等了一輩子的姑娘  來吧
The lass that I have waited my whole life for? Come!
快過來
Come!
請伸出你的腳
Please, present your foot.
怎麼了
What?
你的痣換了一邊
Your mole switched cheeks.
哦  這
Oh, it's...
這是我們家族中的女性都會經歷的事
It happens to all the Snow women.
我們  呃  我們不喜歡談論這些
We just, ahem, we just don't like to talk about it.
好吧
Okay. Uh...
好了  把你的腳抬起來
Okay, yeah, bring your foot up.
很好  繼續
Good. And...
非常適合
A perfect fit!
太好了  現在我們站起來  走到前面
Okay, and now we get up, we come up,
準備好轉圈
and get ready for the spin.
終於找到你了  我的公主
I have found you, my princess!
你不用再穿這些破布了
And you shall never wear rags again!
到你了
Come on.
來  來  來
Come, come, come.
不用擔心  你的僊女教母在這裏
Never fear, your fairy godmother is here.
讓別人看到真實的你吧
Let others see you as I do.
轉圈
Twirl.
-轉圈  -趕緊的
- Twirl. - Come on.
像我教你那樣輕甩手腕
Flick the wrist, like I showed you--
轉圈
Twirl!
蒼天啊  各位  快救火  拜託了
For cryin' out loud, people! Aah! Fix this! Please!
我們從頭再來一次
And let's take it from the top.
貝拉
Bella...
她去哪兒了
Now where is she?
你畫錯痣的位置了
So you put the mole in the wrong s--
喬吉
Georgie?
好吧  我自己來
Okay. Here we go.
喬吉  你  你在這幹嘛
Georgie, what are-- What are you doing here?
泰莎
Well, Tessa...
裏德在找你  我就看下自己能不能幫上忙
Reed was looking for you so I offered to help.
好吧  好吧
Um, right, right.
我會
I will, um...
我  泰莎  接下來的事就交給我吧
I, Tessa, will take it from here.
-多謝了  喬吉  -不客氣
- Thank you, Georgie. - You're welcome.
抱歉了
Sorry. Oh.
還好吧  你臉看上去很紅
Are you okay? You look a little bit flushed.
我沒事
It's ok
沒事就好
Ah, you're okay.
你們看到貝拉了嗎  她不見了
Have you seen Bella? She's AWOL.
沒看到
Uh, no.
她會回來的  她答應過我不會再失蹤的
No, she'll be back. She promised not to disappear again.
是啊  承諾有啥用
Yeah, right. So much for promises.
我想說什麼來著
Um, where was I? Oh...
你知道嗎  我
You know what, I--
我剛剛好像看到貝拉了
I think I, uh, I just saw Bella,
我還是去確認一下
And I think I should probably just go check on her
不要啊  別走
No, don't go,
拜託了  我馬上要去排練了
please. I've got to go and perform in a minute.
就一會兒  我馬上就回來
Um, this will just take a second. I'll be right back.
可讓我找到你了
There you are!
迪萬  嗨
Divine! Hi!
我知道你想幹嘛
Oh, I know what you were doing.
-是嗎  -當然
- You do?  - Yes.
這雙眼睛看透了一切
These eyes see everything.
是嗎
You do.
我知道你幻想著自己
Ooh, I know you have your own little fantasies
能夠站在舞台上  但是
about being up on stage, but, heh,
偷偷溜進灰姑娘的貴賓休息室
lurking around the VIP area of Cinderella is just...
也太可悲了  坦白說  有點嚇人
sad, and frankly, a little creepy.
的確是  你說的對  我很抱歉
Right. Yeah. Of course. Um, I'm so sorry.
-我明白了  不會再這樣了  -那就好
- No more creeping. Understood. - Oh, good.
禮服在哪裏
Now, where are those gowns?
-禮服  -哦  禮服
- The gowns! - Oh, the gowns!
-禮服在哪裏  -禮服  其實
- Where are the gowns? - The gowns. I was about
我正要去拿禮服
to pick the gowns up, actually.
你也可以一起來  不過
You could come with, unless, of course,
你不想被人看到你在服務區吧
you don't wanna be seen in, you know, the service area.
五分鐘內送到套房來
Have them in the suite in five minutes.
你得幫我們穿好
You need to help us get dressed.
好的  我知道了
Yes, of course, heh.
對不起  我來晚了  我得找更多聯繫人
Sorry I'm late. I had to find more contacts.
-沒關係  -快結束了嗎
- It's okay. - Is this almost over?
還沒  現在我必須同時出現在三個地方了
No. Now I need to be in three places at once.
這就是我所說的明星魅力
Now that's what I call star power.
轉起來  姑娘們  散發你們的魅力
Twirl, girls, twirl for Sparkles.
對了  泰莎
Oh, Tessa.
我有東西給你
I have something for you.
-給我的  -我怎麼會忘記你呢  泰莎
- For me? - I didn't forget you, Tessa.
拿去吧
There you go.
沒有服裝要怎麼參加化裝舞會呢
You can't go to a costume ball without a costume.
謝謝你  迪萬
Wow. Thank you, Divine.
你太客氣了
You're so welcome.
哦  我們會給他們  哦  我們會給他們
Oh, we gonna give 'em Oh, we gonna give 'em
我們會給他們
We gonna give 'em
可以談論的話題
S-somethin' somethin' Somethin' to talk about
我們會給他們  哦  我們會給他們
We gonna give 'em Oh, we gonna give 'em
哦  我們會給他們  哦  我們會給他們
Oh, we gonna give 'em Oh, we gonna give 'em
可以談論的話題
S-somethin' somethin' Somethin' to talk about
穿著古馳和普拉達走進大門
Walk in the door Rockin' Gucci and that Prada
男孩們想要大聲吶喊
Your homeboys They tryin' to holler...
好了  姑娘們  準備好光彩奪目吧
All right, girls. Let the dazzling begin.
挺直身子  微笑
Stand up straight. Smile.
抬頭挺胸
Chest forward.
別擋我路  大傢伙  哈哈哈
Outta my way, big baby! Ha-ha-ha!
我們會給他們
And we gonna give 'em
這裏有很多灰姑娘
Oh, there's a lot of Cinderellas here.
姑娘們  站我後面
You girls, in the back.
勇敢點  奧林匹亞
Gallantry, Olympia
大家好
Hello.
我謹代表哈爾斯頓和皇家瀉湖度假酒店
On behalf of the Halstons and Royal Lagoons Resorts,
歡迎各位來到貴賓化妝舞會
welcome to the VIP Costume Ball!
首先  有個小問題
First, one little question.
有人準備好放鬆了嗎
Is anyone in this room ready to get loose?
好了  音樂響起來
Okay. Play the music.
我看見你在凝視這裏
I see you there Staring here
舞動起來  你在害怕什麼
Make a move Why are you scared?
忘記時間  盡情放縱自我
Push yourself Forget the clock
醒來以前  仍有大把時光
We got all night Then still wake up
散下秀髮   只為今晚狂歡
Let down your hair For just one night
來吧  你在害羞什麼
Come on, now Why are you still shy?
我看見你在凝視這裏
I see you there Staring here
舞動起來
Make a move
動起來  寶貝  放鬆  放鬆
Come on, baby Get loose, loose
忘掉煩惱
Let it go
放鬆  在舞池裏放縱自我
Get loose, loose On the floor
放鬆  盡情享受人生樂趣
Get loose, loose Have some fun
夜色才剛剛降臨
The night has just begun
動起來  寶貝  放鬆  放鬆
Come on, baby Get loose, loose
忘掉煩惱
Let it go
放鬆  在舞池裏放縱自我
Get loose, loose On the floor
放鬆  盡情享受人生樂趣
Get loose, loose Have some fun
好有趣的裝扮
Interesting choice of costume.
我是只企鵝
I'm a penguin.
是  我看出來了
Yes, you are.
你能溜走嗎
Can you sneak away?
這樣我們就能把車修好了
Uh, so we can, uh, finish the bike.
我會找個機會溜出去的
I'll waddle out somehow.
泰莎
Tessa?
-怎麼了  -我頭髮掉了
- Yeah? - My hair broke.
你得幫我把它接回去
You have to help me put it back together.
給我五分鐘
Five minutes.
你和你那個神秘女孩怎麼樣了
How's your mystery girl working out for you?
她是個天才  但是有點古怪
She's talented but she's flaky.
她肯定有自己的原因
Oh, I'm sure she has her reasons.
是啊
Yeah.
可能我更喜歡我能信任的人吧
Maybe I'd just prefer someone I can trust.
她有趣
Someone who's funny.
喜歡笑
Likes to laugh.
也很聰明
Smart, of course.
身手還很敏捷
Smartenly probably.
超級可愛
Who's amazingly cute.
走起路來搖搖晃晃的
And waddles.
我覺得車沒問題了
I think that should do it.
你想騎上去試試嗎
You wanna try and start her up?
不用了  你來吧
No, you take the honors.
你修好了
You did it!
我們修好了  我們成功了
We did it. We totally did it.
那哈珀怎麼辦
What about Harper?
你在這兒呢
There you are!
你現在應該和豪斯頓家族會面
You're supposed to be meeting with the Halstons right now.
沒錯
Uh? Oh, yeah.
我忘記時間了
Um, I lost track of time.
能等我一分鐘嗎
Can you give me one minute?
你需要一分鐘啊
Oh, you need a minute?
當然可以  當然  慢慢
By all means, yeah, take all the--
不行  一分鐘也不行
No, you can't have a minute!
我們不能讓金主等著  裏德
We don't keep the big money waiting, Reed.
我過會兒給你打電話
I'll call you later.
快走  快走
Let's go. Let's go.
弗雷迪
Freddie?
那個  豪斯頓家族
The-- The Halstons...
哈珀也會來嗎
Um, will Harper be there?
會  她要飛過來  給裏德一個驚喜
Yes, she's flying out to surprise Reed.
我安排的
I arranged it.
所以他們  他們在一起了
So they're-- They're together.
泰莎
Oh, Tessa.
我知道待在裏德這樣的男孩子身邊的時間肯定很短暫
I know it must be a rush being around a guy like Reed.
我是說  他馬上就要成為巨星了
I mean, he's about to become a huge star--
這個我一點都不在乎
I couldn't care less about that.
哈珀才是合適他的人
--which is exactly why Harper is so right for him.
聽著  我不知道裏德跟你說了什麼
Look, I don't know what Reed told you,
但是我確信他月底就要求婚了
but I'm pretty sure he's gonna propose by the end of the month.
什麼
What?
很抱歉  泰莎  真的抱歉
I'm sorry, Tessa. Really.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我怎麼這麼傻
How could I have been so stupid?
結束了  我不演了
Well, I'm done. I'm done with the show.
我和裏德也算完了  也和貝拉·斯諾徹底說再見
I'm done with Reed. Definitely done with Bella Snow.
演出不能沒有貝拉
The show can't go on without Bella.
他很聰明  能想到辦法的
He's resourceful. He'll figure something out.
說曹操曹操到
Unh. Speaking of...
聽著  事情的關鍵在你自己
Look, this is about you.
你假冒貝拉·斯諾  就是為了一個男孩子嗎
Did you become Bella Snow to win a boy?
不  不是  我假冒貝拉是因為我
No. No, I became Bella Snow because I was--
你在追逐自己的夢想
You were following your dream.
弗雷迪點醒了我  喬吉
Freddie was a real wake-up call, Georgie.
我什麼都不是  也就會自欺欺人而已
I'm nobody. With just enough talent to delude myself.
泰莎  你自己決定
Oh, Tessa, it's your decision.
但是你要是現在放棄了  直到你死的那一天
But if you give up now, you'll always wonder,
你都會想  我要是沒放棄會怎樣呢
to your dying day, what if?
天啊  我好想你
God, I miss you.
你要是在這兒就好了  爸爸
I wish you were here, Dad.
也不一定是指在這兒
Well, not exactly here.
你要是我  會怎麼做
What would you do if you were me?
我是這樣一個人
I've never been one
不曾踏出自己的舒適圈
To step out Of my comfort zone
每次努力時  都擔心自己止步不前
Whenever I try I'm afraid to just let go
我不知道我為什麼逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我為什麼隱藏
Don't know why I hide
不讓他人知曉自己真實的內心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不知道我為什麼恐懼
Don't know why I'm scared
當我站立於此
Just to take a chance
只能放手一搏
While I'm still standing here
我是這樣一個人
I've never been one
不曾掙脫束縛自由翱翔
To break free
因為我總是在意他人的目光
'Cause I've always cared What everyone thinks of me
我不知道我為什麼逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我為什麼隱藏
Don't know why I hide
不讓他人知曉自己真實的內心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不想放棄  我不想逃走
I don't want to settle Don't want to run
這裏不是我的歸宿
This is not Where I belong
演得很好
Well done.
就是  我知道自己的白馬王子愛上別人之後
It's just-- It's hard to be Cinderella when I know
再演灰姑娘就太難了
my prince charming is in love with someone else.
冷靜點  先把演出搞定
Get a grip. And focus on what's important.
你說得對
Yeah, you're right.
上台  讓他們看看真正的你
Go back out there and show 'em who are you.
-好嗎  -好
-Okay？ - Okay.
走吧
Let's go.
你明白現在的狀況嗎
Do you get what's going on?
不明白
No.
這就對了  我們就是刻薄
That's right. We're mean.
我們不喜歡你  就得給你來硬的
We don't like you. You're a hardball.
喬吉
Georgie?
小莎  我在你房間等你  情況緊急  -喬
喬
Georg--
迪萬
Divine.
你好呀  "貝拉"
Cheerio, "Bella."
我就知道  你身上是餅乾的味道
I knew you smelled like cookies.
你覺得你能逃得掉嗎
Did you really think you could get away with this?
雅典娜身上流淌著成為明星的血液
Athena has the blood of a star running through her veins,
她一定會得到她應有的角色
and she will take her rightful place.
迪萬  求求你別這樣
Divine, please don't do this.
"求求你別這樣  迪萬"
"Please don't do this, Divine."
迪萬  別  別  別這樣
Divine, no. No, no, no, no.
別這樣  迪萬  求你了
No, Divine, please!
迪萬
Divine!
有人聽得見嗎
Please, can someone hear me?
快點  想辦法  泰莎  快想
Come on, think, Tessa, think.
喬吉  泰莎還好嗎
Georgie, is Tessa all right?
她不接我電話  也不回我短信
She's not answering my calls or texts.
你要是真在乎她  為什麼不問弗雷迪
If you really care, why don't you ask Freddie?
她就是我的命中注定
She's the one.
但是王子  我們怎麼才能找到她
But how do we find her, my prince?
我們要找遍整個王國
We must search the land
找到那位能穿下這只水晶鞋的少女
to find the lovely maiden whose delicate foot fits this glass slipper.
我知道人們會說
I know they say
有時候一個尺寸人人適合
That sometimes That one size fits all
但是這裏只有一位姑娘
But there's Only one girl in here
能夠在舞會上艷壓群芳
That's fit to be The belle of the ball
只有一位姑娘
There can only be one
在清晨的鐘聲敲響之前
So I'm looking for The right one
我要找尋到那命定之人
Before the end Of the night, sir
我要所有姑娘都聚起來
I need every girl To gather around
收起左腳  伸出右腳
Put your left in the crown Stick out the right one
我只需要你們  自然而然地穿上
'Cause all I need is you To slip, slip on slide 'em on
時間所剩無幾  快點吧
'Cause we don't really Have much time, come on
當十二點的鐘聲響起  那就為時已晚
When the clock hits 12 Major fail
三  二  一  好了  就現在
Three, two, one Okay, now
烏拉  呼啦  烏拉  呼啦
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
我不確定  誰才是她
Which girl's the one Man, I don't know
烏拉  呼啦  烏拉  呼啦
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
到底是誰  才穿得下
Who's got the foot That'll rock the sole
鞋若合腳  就快穿上
Well, if the shoe fits Then go put it on
快穿上
Go put it on
鞋若合腳  就快穿上
Well, if the shoe fits Then go put it on
快穿上
Go put it on
你知道的  鞋若合腳
Well, if the shoe fits you You know what to do
快穿上
Put it on
貝拉怎麼沒在候場
Why isn't Bella in position?
我不知道  我正等著給她換衣服
I don't know. I've been waiting to dress her in--
她的演出服去哪兒了
Where's her costume?
你怎麼回事
What is wrong with you?
-你怎麼這麼胖  -衣服太小了
- Why are you so fat? - It's so small.
我來試試
Let me try.
奧林匹亞  幫我們盯著
Olympia, keep watch!
我為什麼不能當灰姑娘
Why can't I be Cinderella?
因為奧林匹亞  你不夠優秀
Because Olympia! You're just not good enough!
等一下  媽媽  誰來演我的角色
Wait, Mom. Who's going to play my part?
歡迎蒞臨蔽捨
Welcome to our humble home.
王子殿下要求房裏
His highness requests the presence
所有女士都出來一下
of all the ladies of the house.
我的兩個女兒和我
My two daughters and I are--
你姐姐呢  親愛的
Where's your sister, dear?
誰在乎  可能她死了吧
Who cares? Maybe she's dead.
不對  我想起來了  她在房間裏
No, I remember. She's in her room.
我真蠢  怎麼把這忘了
Silly me. How could I forget?
我是說  她遠在底特律
I meant she's far, far away in Detroit.
停  等等  等等
Wait! Hold on, hold on.
我在這兒呢  母親
Here I am, Mother!
繼續找  一定要找到貝拉
Just keep going! And find Bella!
在皇家水晶鞋試穿日去底特律  怎麼可能
...Detroit, when it's Royal Try-on-a-Glass-Shoe Day?
明明有菲力牛排
Why waste your princely time on ground beef
還在碎牛肉上浪費什麼時間呢
when you could have filet mignon?
別害怕  我不咬人
Don't be afraid. I don't bite.
可能  就這裏那裏隨便摸摸吧
Well, maybe a little bit here and there.
其實  我只是喜歡擁抱別人
Actually, I'm just all cuddles.
快點  問我妹妹
Go ahead, ask my sister.
恐怕我沒法問這個問題了
That doesn't appear to be an option.
什麼
Huh?
外邊怎麼了
What is happening out there?
我會讓母親知道  我足夠優秀
I'll show Mom I'm good enough!
別拽了
Stop it!
你把一切都毀了
You're ruining everything!
你個壞姑娘  滾過來
Aah, you evil girl, come back here!
唉  鞋不合腳
Alas, it does not fit.
你確定嗎  王子
Are you sure, Prince?
非常  非常確定
Really, really sure.
那就塞進去
Cram it in.
我不管  快去找人
Okay, I don't care, just do it.
不好意思  我要去餵馬了
Uh, excuse me, I must go feed the horses.
哈嘍  小傢伙
Hello, guy.
我現在遇到點麻煩
Okay. So I'm kind of in a situation right now.
甜心  你能告訴我走哪條路嗎
And you gotta tell me which way to go, sugar,
那邊還是這邊
that way or this way?
好了  走吧
Oh, okay. Here we go.
不行  我不在乎  演出不能叫停
No, I don't care. We're not gonna stop the show.
去  快去
Just do it, do it!
你幹什麼呢  你得去舞台上
What are you doing? I need you out there!
你先告訴我  你和泰莎說什麼了
First tell me what you said to Tessa.
泰莎  裏德  演出都一團糟了
Tessa? Reed, the show's a mess.
我找不到貝拉  她們幹嘛呢
I can't find Bella-- What are they doing?
-我不知道  也不在乎  -這很重要
- I don't know and I don't care. - This is important.
你在哪兒呢呀  寶貝王子
Where you are, Prince dear.
你給我出來  不然我就砍了你
Get out here or I will cut you!
你跟她說什麼了  告訴我
What did you say to her? Just tell me.
出  去
Go! Out!
不好
Oh, no.
別  別  別  別
No, no, no, no.
好了  如果房內沒有其他女士
Right, if there are no other ladies in the house,
我們就該走了
then we must take our leave.
除非  聽  你聽見什麼聲音了嗎
Unless, hark, do you hear something?
也許吧
Um, maybe?
我很肯定  我聽到什麼了
I'm sure I must have heard a noise!
真要這樣麼
Ow. Ow. Really?
我有錯過試穿水晶鞋嗎
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
哈嘍  我有錯過試穿
Oh, hello. Am I too late to try on--
我有錯過試穿水晶鞋嗎
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
我的天吶  你發什麼瘋
Oh, my God! What has gotten in to you?
停下  不行
Stop it, no!
我不會上台了
I'm not going back out there
除非你告訴我  你和泰莎說了什麼
until you tell me what you said to Tessa.
不行
No!
好吧  我是說了點
Okay. I may have said something
你和哈珀訂婚的事兒
about you and Harper getting engaged.
-就這樣  -為什麼  弗雷迪
- That's all. - Why, Freddie?
-你為什麼和泰莎說那些  -你們  把麥遮住
- Why would you say that to Tessa? - Guys, cover your mic.
注意了  各位  敬請欣賞新版《灰姑娘》
Hold on, everybody, get ready for the new Cinderella.
你馬上就要成為巨星了
You're on the verge of stardom.
裏德  我都是為了你啊
Reed, I did it for you.
我知道你是好心  弗雷迪
I know you mean well, Freddie,
但是輪不到你為我做決定
but you do not get to make those calls for me.
哈珀就是我的朋友  我對她不是那種喜歡
Harper's just a friend, I don't like her that way.
不行
No!
泰莎  她挺好的  但是那有什麼大不了的
Tessa, I mean, she's sweet, but what's the big deal?
重要的是  人生中第一次
The big deal is, for the first time in my life,
我墜入愛河了
I think I'm in love!
沒有人願意孤身一人
Nobody ever wants To be alone
因為我們都想要一個知心好友
'Cause we all want A friend to call our own
貝拉
Bella?
我有錯過試穿水晶鞋嗎
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
泰莎
Tessa?
你是灰姑娘
You're Cinderella?
抱歉  沒有告訴你我的真實身份
I'm sorry I didn't tell you who I really was.
我從沒想過像你這樣的王子
I never thought that a prince like you
會愛上我這樣的女孩
could ever love girl like me.
我更抱歉  讓你受了苦
Not as sorry as I am, to have caused you any pain.
我的參謀  弗雷德裏科  沒有告訴我
My advisor, Frederico spoke not the truth
有關婚禮的實情
of my impending nuptials.
弗雷迪說我要和哈珀訂婚的事  是假的
Freddie totally lied about me getting married to Harper.
我聽到了
I heard.
在這個王國  聲音能傳很遠
Sound travels quite well in this kingdom.
請來試試水晶鞋吧
Please, try on the glass slipper.
樂意之至
I'd love to.
你知道嗎  我不需要一隻鞋來告訴我
You know what? I don't need a shoe to tell me
我內心的感覺
what I really feel in my heart.
你就是我的命中注定
You're the one.
別拍了
Stop it!
別拍了  你噁心死了
Stop it, you're disgusting.
不要害怕  你的僊女教母已經到來
Never fear, your fairy godmother is here.
讓世界看到真實的你吧
Let the world see you as I do.
轉圈
Twirl.
太好了
Yes! Come on.
你的僊女教母做得很好
Your fairy godmother does great work.
那是當然
She really does.
我是這樣一個人
I've never been one
不曾踏出自己的舒適圈
To step out Of my comfort zone
每次努力時  都擔心自己止步不前
Whenever I try I'm afraid to just let go
我不知道我為什麼逃跑
Don't know why I run
我不知道我為什麼隱藏
Don't know why I hide
不讓他人知曉自己真實的內心
Never let them know What I feel inside
我不想放棄  我不想逃走
I don't want to settle Don't want to run
這裏
This is not
不是我的歸宿
Where I belong
如同飛鳥  我注定飛翔
Like a bird I need to fly
張開雙翼  尋找生命的意義
Spread my wings And find my life
如同飛鳥  我飛入高空
Like a bird I'm up so high
飛出牢籠  是時候大放異彩
Out of the cage It's my time to shine
是時候大放異彩
It's my time to shine
如同飛鳥  我自由飛翔
Like a bird I'm free to fly
所以告訴我  告訴我  我為什麼要逃避
So tell me, tell me Why don't I?
如同飛鳥  我自由飛翔
Like a bird Free to fly
張開雙翼  尋找生命的意義
Spread my wings Find my life
如同飛鳥  我飛入高空
Like a bird Up so high
飛出牢籠  是時候大放異彩
Out the cage It's time to shine
張開雙翼  尋找生命的意義
Spread my wings Find my life
如同飛鳥  我飛入高空
Like a bird Up so high
飛出牢籠  是時候大放異彩
Out the cage It's time to shine
如同飛鳥  我飛入高空
Like a bird Up so high
飛出牢籠  是時候大放異彩
Out the cage It's time to shine
給我打電話
Call me.
謝謝你
Thank you.
表演太棒了
That was incredible.
我太為你驕傲了
I'm so proud of you.
喬吉  我不知道怎麼才能謝你
Georgie, I don't know how to thank you.
用不著
You don't have to.
也許你需要這個
I thought you might need this.
你最好了  沒有你我該怎麼辦
You're the best. What would I do without you?
抱歉  兄弟  我搞砸了
Sorry, buddy. I messed up.
如果你不想讓我當你的經紀人了
But if you don't want me to be your manager anymore,
我也能理解的
I'll understand.
不  我當然需要了
No, of course I do.
另外  也許你甚至還有機會
Plus, you may even get the chance
和一位有才華的新星一起工作呢
to work with a talented new star.
嘿  帥哥  我們走吧
Hey, charming, let's bounce.
尋找生命的意義
Found my life
寶貝  我們做到了
Sweety, we did it.
我知道我不能獨佔所有功勞  但是
I know I can't take all the credit, but...
要是沒有我  也不會這麼成功不是嗎
it certainly wouldn't have happened without me, right?
迪萬  你是所有女孩心中
Divine, you've been the best evil stepmother
惡毒後媽的典範
a girl could ever ask for, but, uh--
謝謝你
Thank you.
我們是時候分道揚鑣了
I think it's definitely time for us to part ways.
記得給我打電話
Call me.
所以  你想去哪兒
So? Where do you wanna go?
大放異彩
Time to shine...
哪裏都想去
Everywhere.
從某方面來看  我們都會遇到一個激動人心的機會
At some point, we all come across an exciting opportunity,
但是我們可能對新的旅途產生畏懼  我的建議呢
a new path that might scare us. My advice?
踩離合器  即刻出發
Pop the clutch, hit the road
努力過上幸福美滿的生活
and make your happily-ever-after come true.
整日忙碌  卻一無所獲
Working all day Don't do a thing
其實你坐在駕駛座  可以掌控自己的生活
Life's what you make it You're in the driver's seat
加大油門  擰動點火
Rev your engine Crank the ignition
給我鑰匙  你怎樣都無法阻止我
Give me the key Don't need your permission
媽媽總是說
Mama always told me
生活中沒什麼好怕的
There's nothing In this life to fear
從懵懵懂懂到無所不能  你將會想念現在的我
You're gonna miss me Zero to sixty
把生活拉回正軌
Kicking it into gear
是我坐在駕駛座  掌控著生活
I'm in control I'm behind the wheel
想去哪裏  就將一往無前
And I'm gonna steer Where I wanna steer
是我坐在駕駛座  掌控著生活
I'm in control I'm behind the wheel
想去哪裏  就將一往無前
And I'm gonna steer Where I'm gonna steer
加足馬力
Go full throttle
活著
Living
活著  活著
Living, living
沒什麼好怕的
Nothing to fear
讓自己走上正軌
Put yourself in gear
加足馬力
Go full throttle
我知道大雨即將落下
I know that rain Is falling
不必滿面愁容
Don't look So sad about it
我知道也許會有點痛
I know It hurts a little
你想要高聲呼喊
You wanna Scream and shout
我有挽救方法
I got the remedy
就跟著節奏一遍一遍盡情搖擺
Just let the rhythm Take you over and over
一遍又一遍
Over and over
我知道你萬分沮喪
I know you're down
我來讓你展開笑顏
Let me pick you up
我知道你很堅強
I know you're strong
我知道你很堅韌
I know you're tough
你想坐在一旁
You wanna sit
但你需要舞動
You need to move
感受音樂  讓我來為你示範
Let me show you how to do it Feel the music
如果你開心  那就鼓掌
Hey, you gotta clap When you're happy
如果你難過 也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
無論開心難過  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顧慮太多
Don't think too much About it
學會放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
說"嘿"的感覺是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
如果你開心  那就鼓掌
Clap when you're happy
如果你難過 也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
無論開心難過  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顧慮太多
Don't think too much About it
學會放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
說"嘿"的感覺是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
我已找到解開困惑的新途徑
I got a new solution To all of this confusion
你會慶幸你加入其中
You'll feel so glad You made it
不要讓事情變得複雜
Don't make it Complicated
這是嶄新的一天
This is a brand new day
就跟著音樂一遍一遍盡情搖擺
Just let the music Take you over and over
一遍又一遍
Over and over
我知道你萬分沮喪
I know you're down
我來讓你展開笑顏
Let me pick you up
我知道你很堅強
I know you're strong
我知道你很堅韌
I know you're tough
你想坐在一旁
You wanna sit
但你需要舞動
You need to move
感受音樂  讓我來為你示範
Let me show you how to do it Feel the music
如果你開心  那就鼓掌
Hey, you gotta clap When you're happy
如果你難過  也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
無論開心難過  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顧慮太多
Don't think too much About it
學會放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
說"嘿"的感覺是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
如果你開心  那就鼓掌
Clap when you're happy
如果你難過  也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
無論開心難過  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顧慮太多
Don't think too much About it
學會放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
說"嘿"的感覺是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say, "Hey"
如果你開心  那就鼓掌
Clap when you're happy
如果你難過  也要鼓掌
Clap when you're sad
無論開心難過  都要鼓掌
Clap when your day is good Or when it's going bad
不要顧慮太多
Don't think too much About it
學會放空自我
Just keep your head In the sky
這感覺是不是妙不可言
Now don't it feel good To say...
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey, hey, hey
哈哈  抱歉
Ha, sorry.